greplin.com 2014-07-28

# Cue - Privacy Policy

#### Policy Effective Dates

##### Effective Date of This Version

June 25, 2012

##### Effective Date of Prior Version

February 29, 2012

#### Introduction

For Cue, protecting your privacy and keeping your data secure isn’t just important, it’s the lifeblood of our company. We believe that your data isn’t a commodity; to us, it is sacred. We strive to make Cue as secure as possible, and to ensure all our decisions respect your privacy. By doing so, we protect not only our users’ data, but our own. Our fierce commitment to privacy is motivated not just by personal and professional reasons, but because we know it’s the right thing to do. We fully appreciate the trust Cue users put in us, and we will do everything we can to earn and maintain that trust.

Cue turns your email, contacts and calendar into an intelligent snapshot of your day. All you need to create a Cue account is an email address. Then you can use OAuth (when available) to add Linked Accounts like Gmail, Yahoo Mail, Google Calendar, Facebook, and many other accounts that you depend on every day. Cue pulls these Linked Accounts together to create a personalized overview of the events and activities of your day. Cue displays everything you need to stay one step ahead: phone numbers, addresses, contact details, conﬁrmation numbers, ﬁles and more. You can also search across Your Data in one convenient place.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to explain (1) how we use and don’t use your login credentials to link Your Data to Cue, (2) how we collect and handle your Personal Information, (3) how we handle and maintain the index of Your Data, (4) how to terminate your account, or delete the index of Your Data, (5) how to work with us to maintain your privacy and the security of your Personal Information and Your Data, and (6) other privacy considerations.

#### Linked Accounts

“Linked Accounts” in this Privacy Policy means any third-party application, like Facebook or Gmail, that you choose to link to your Cue account. A complete list of supported Linked Accounts can be found here.

#### Your Personal Information

“Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy means any information that can be used to identify and/or contact you, and information regarding your use of the Service that may be connected with you. Depending on how you use the Service, Personal Information may include your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address, postal address, calendar appointments, and your personal and/or business contacts. Personal Information may also include information we gather regarding how your use the Service.

#### Your Data

“Your Data” in this Privacy Policy means the electronic files and items that you have created and/or stored using Linked Accounts. When you link one of those accounts to Cue, we index Your Data so that it can be more easily accessible to you. Depending on how you use the service, this can include emails, calendar events, personal and/or business contacts, documents, spreadsheets, notes, messages, status updates, tweets and posts. Cue currently does not index audio/video files, but does index titles and other information associated with such files, like the file type. Cue may also index information associated with Your Data that you might not usually see, like time stamps and labels.

#### 1\. Your Login Credentials

In order to index Your Data, we must be able to access your Linked Accounts. In most cases we are able to access your accounts without ever seeing or storing your login credentials by using the OAuth authentication protocol. You can learn more about OAuth here.

#### OAuth-Compatible Services

Almost all of the Linked Accounts that Cue indexes are OAuth compatible. When you instruct Cue to index Your Data from a service that supports OAuth, you will be required to log in to that Linked Account using your username and password. For example, if you instruct Cue to index Your Data from Facebook, you will be required to log in to Facebook with your Facebook username and password. This confirms that you are the owner of that account and have the authorization to let Cue access the account. Your login also generates a unique authorization token that allows Cue to access that account and index Your Data. Cue does not actually see or store your login credentials; Cue only utilizes the unique authorization token generated by the OAuth protocol. Cue uses the token to automatically create an index of Your Data from the Linked Account, and update the index on an ongoing basis so that your Cue account is always up to date. You have the ability to turn this token off at any time. You have two ways to shut off Cue’s access to any given Linked Account at any time: (1) changing the setting on the Linked Account’s setting page, or (2) changing the setting in your Cue account. As of the effective date of this Privacy Policy, all Linked Accounts that Cue can index for you are OAuth compatible except the ones listed here.

#### Non-OAuth-Compatible Services

In situations where the Linked Account does not offer OAuth, Cue utilizes the login credentials you provide to us. Cue only uses these login credentials to keep the index of Your Data up to date, and encrypts your credentials using military-grade AES-128 encryption.

#### 2\. How We Collect and Use Your Personal Information

You provide Personal Information to Cue in several ways:

#### Account Registration

When you create a Cue account, you provide us with a verifiable email address and password of your choice. If you upgrade to Cue Premium, you additionally provide us with your full name and payment verification information, including address, credit card number, and card expiration date.

#### Log Information

When you use Cue, we automatically record information about your device, its software, and your use of Cue. This may include your device’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, identification numbers associated with your device, browser type, the web page visited before you came to our website, locale preferences, your mobile carrier, and metadata concerning Your Data. If you use Cue from your mobile device, you have the option of letting us know your location. If you choose this option, we may keep records of location information in order to provide location-dependent information like sunrise times and weather updates.

#### Cookies

Like most other websites, Cue uses cookies to help improve the Cue Service. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. These text files are used by these websites and help identify you when you return to a website. Cookies can be “persistent” or “session” based. Persistent cookies remain on your computer when you have gone offline, while session cookies are deleted as soon as you close your web browser. You can set your browser to stop accepting cookies, but this may effect functionality and limit your ability to fully utilize the Cue Service.

As of the effective date of this Privacy Policy, Cue uses the Google Analytics web analytics service. Google Analytics uses cookies to help us understand how Cue is utilized. Google uses the information generated by these cookie to evaluate use of the website, compile reports for us on website activity and provide other services relating to website activity and internet usage. You can find more information on Google Analytics [here](http://www.google.com/analytics/), and a link to Google’s privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). 

#### Use of Your Personal Information

It is our policy to never disclose personally identifiable information except as specified in this Privacy Policy. Cue may use your Personal Information to (1) provide, monitor, analyze, and improve the Cue Service, (2) personalize and improve your user experience, and (3) verify that you have the authorization needed for us to process your requests. In some cases Cue may also use your Personal Information to provide software updates and product announcements. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in any of those communications, or update your account settings here.

Cue uses the following trusted third-party service providers:

\- Amazon Web Services (AWS) for cloud hosting

\- Google for Google Analytics

\- Stripe for credit card processing

These service providers may have access to certain Personal Information solely for purposes of performing these tasks on Cue’s behalf and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy.

#### Non-Identifiable Personal Information

Cue will never disclose personally identifiable information except as specified in this Privacy Policy. We may disclose aggregated or otherwise non-identifiable information, like Cue usage statistics, to third parties.

#### How Cue Handles and Maintains Your Data

After you authorize access of your Linked Accounts, Cue processes Your Data using advanced algorithms, then creates an indexed version of Your Data. If you revoke Cue’s Oauth access through a Linked Account’s settings page, and not directly through Cue, we will immediately stop indexing all data from that Linked Account. However, this does not affect the index of Your Data prior to that moment. In order to permanently remove your index from Cue, you must delete the Linked Account from Cue on our settings page.

#### Data Security Systems

The security of Your Data is of paramount importance to Cue. Cue takes extraordinary steps to protect Your Data. That’s why we utilize a variety of technologies that provide significant protection against network security issues like Distributed Denial of Services (DDoS) attacks, Man in the Middle (MITM) attacks, and packet sniffing. Cue delivers your indexed data to you utilizing a secure channel using 256-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption, the current standard for secure internet network connections. In addition to the security measures publicly detailed in this Privacy Policy, Cue is constantly innovating and keeps up to date with the innovations of others in this field.

#### Employee Access to Your Data

In order to improve Cue’s algorithms, select Cue employees occasionally review aggregate user data that has been automatically stripped of all personally identifiable information. This allows us to find patterns that distinguish between, for example, an email from an airline about an upcoming trip and an email from an airline about a discounted fare. We have built extensive proprietary systems to prevent employees from accessing Your Data. In the unlikely event that any of our measures should fail, the unauthorized access is logged and flagged, and senior members of our staff are alerted.

#### Partner Access to Your Data

Cue utilizes Amazon as our cloud services provider, meaning that the index of Your Data resides on secure Amazon servers. Amazon employees are not authorized to access Your Data, and we have taken measures, where possible, to protect Your Data from Amazon employees. You can find more information on Amazon’s data security policies [here](http://aws.amazon.com/security/).

#### Compliance with Laws

Cue will only disclose Your Data to third parties when required to do so to comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request. If we are required by law to provide Your Data to a law enforcement agency, we may also be required to remove any encryption before providing that data to the agency. If we are required by law to disclose Your Data to a third party, it is our policy to provide you with notice of this disclosure, unless prohibited by law.

#### Business Transfers

If Cue is ever involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Your Data and Personal Information may be transferred as part of that transaction. If that happens we will notify you using the email address associated with your user account. If you are not comfortable with this transfer, you will have the option to terminate your account or delete selected portions of Your Data.

#### 4\. Account Termination; Deleting Data

You can terminate your entire Cue account, or just delete a single Linked Account, rapidly and easily in your Cue settings. Once you instruct us to delete a Linked Account, Cue will promptly remove the index of Your Data, unless retention of Your Data is necessary for Cue to comply with legal obligations and/or resolve disputes. If Cue needs to retain Your Data in one of these exceptional circumstances, we will notify you using the email address associated with your user account.

#### 5\. You Must Work With Cue to Secure Your Personal Information and Data

Although Cue goes to great lengths to protect your Personal Information and Your Data through its policies, procedures, and the design of its infrastructure, we cannot keep your account safe without your participation.

#### Protect Your Cue Login Credentials

Cue is responsible for the secure operation of the Service, but you are responsible for the security of your login credentials. We strongly recommend that you never share your login credentials with others. If for any reason you believe that your login credentials have fallen into the wrong hands, you should immediately access your account and change your password. If you believe that a third-party has locked you out of your own account, contact us at [security@CueUp.com](mailto:security@CueUp.com). Keeping the login credentials for your Linked Accounts is just as important as safeguarding your Cue account.

#### Check Your Account Activity Log

On your settings page, Cue displays an account activity log that shows recent account activity. The Account Activity log displays when your account was accessed, the device through which it was accessed, and the IP address from which your account was accessed. We encourage you to regularly check your activity log for suspicious activity. If it appears that a third party has accessed your Cue account without your authorization, immediately change your password. You can also report suspicious activity to Cue by emailing [security@CueUp.com](mailto:security@CueUp.com).

#### Access to Employer Data

You should get permission from your employer before using Cue to index a Linked Account that is associated with your employment, like a Salesforce account. If we receive a verifiable request from an employer requesting that we remove a work-related Linked Account from your Cue indexes, we reserve the right to comply with such a request. This could happen if, for example, you change employers but continue to index a Linked Account associated with the former employer.

#### 6\. Other Privacy Considerations

#### We Do Not Collect Personal Information from Children Under 13

The Cue Service is not directed to persons under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, you should contact us at [support@CueUp.com](mailto:support@CueUp.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will take steps to delete such information from our files.

#### Linked Accounts

Each of your Linked Accounts has its own privacy policy which likely differs from Cue’s Privacy Policy. Given that Your Data is created with and/or stored within those Linked Accounts, you should familiarize yourself with the terms of service and privacy policy for each Linked Account you use. Some Linked Accounts may have features that allow you to adjust your privacy settings for that account (for example, whether Your Data is private, visible only to select persons, or available to anyone on the internet). When you instruct Cue to index Your Data from a certain Linked Account, all of the data in that account is indexed and made available for you to access via Cue. If you terminate a Linked Account from within that Linked Account, Cue will no longer index it. Your Cue Account, however, will still contain an index of Your Data from before you terminated that Linked Account. If you want that data deleted from your index, you can request a deletion from within your Cue Account. If you change your privacy settings for a particular Linked Account, that doesn’t change what Cue has already indexed, and does not change what Cue indexes going forward; what you see when you access a particular Linked Account is still being indexed until you delete that data from your Cue Account.

#### What Data is Public?

Nothing. There are no private/public/friends-only settings on Cue. Unregistered visitors to the website see only information about the Cue Service. No unauthorized 3rd parties can see Your Data in your Cue account, or even know that you have an account, unless you share that information or lose exclusive control of your login credentials.

#### International Users

Cue is an online service based in the U.S., and our offices are headquartered in the U.S. Please be aware that information you provide to us and the data that we index as a result of your use of the Cue Service will be processed in and transferred to the U.S. and be subject to U.S. law. The privacy and data protection laws in the U.S. may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. By visiting the Website, downloading a Cue App, utilizing the Cue Services, or by providing us with your Personal Information or Your Data, you consent to this collection, transfer, storage, and processing of information to and in the U.S.

#### Invitations

You may elect to invite friends to try Cue using our invitation feature. When you use this feature, we send a one-time invitation to try the service to your invitee using the email address that you provide.

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If Cue makes a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will provide you with notice using the email address associated with your user account. We will also revise the Privacy Policy effective date noted at the top of this page when we make changes. By continuing to use the Cue Service after changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the revised Privacy Policy, you should terminate your Cue account.

#### Questions?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@CueUp.com](mailto:support@CueUp.com).
